Hasmukh Shah

Front-end Developer

Phone: 8200899614

Address: Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

Website: https://pekskumar.github.io/Has

mukh_React_Portfolio/

Email: hasmukhweb19@gmail.com

I've been working from 1.9+ year as a Frontend Developer. During that time I've been trained software platforms and systems. I have experience in React Js, Javascript, WordPress, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Tailwind, React Bootstrap, Jquery and Bootstrap. I am Passionate about implementing and launching new projects. Looking to start the career as Full-Stack Frontend Developer with a reputed firm driven by technology.

EXPERIENCES

OpensourceXpert InfoTech, Ahmedabad

February 2022 - Present

Frontend Developer

- Expand features, refine code, and improve processes, producing smoother operations and enhancing user engagement.
- I've experience in third party REST API Integration to scale up the React SPA, React PWA and React SSR Applications.
- Authentication and authorization using react components in web app.
- Develop web applications according to client briefs and modify designs to meet changes in client specifications.
- Developing dynamic and browser compatible pages using React Js, Javascript, HTML5, Tailwind, React Bootstrap, SASS, CSS3, Bootstrap and jQuery.
- Collaborated with web designers, back end developers and UX designers to design, build, test and improve web products.
- · Assisted in the training of new developers and web designers.
- Ensure efficient web development by supporting designers and app developers while resolving website performance issues.
- · Ability to write Effectively, clean, minimalistic, reusable code.
- Utilized Adobe Photoshop, XD and Figma for the production of web-optimized Images.
- Maintained accuracy and attention to detail throughout the creative and development process.
- Handled multiple projects simultaneously while ensuring all projects were completed within the deadline date.

TOPS Technologies Pvt. Ltd, Ahmedabad

March 2021 - December 2021

Web Developer

- Designing new logos
- Developing different website pages with the help of html5,css3,bootstrap and jQuery
- Responsive website using Media Jquery

DESIGN & CODING

Coding Skill

React Js

Redux

HTML

CSS

Tailwind

SASS

jQuery Javascript **Bootstrap Design Skill** Figma XD Photoshop Material UI Illustrator Wordpress **ChatGPT Skill Highlights** Web Development **Cross Browser Operability** Project management **Process Improvement Workflow Optimization User Requirements Gathering Login Flow** https://pekskumar.github.io/hasmukh-LoginFlow/ **Browser Datastore** https://pekskumar.github.io/Hasmukh_Browser_Datastore/ Manage_Employees https://pekskumar.github.io/Hasmukh_Manage_Employees/ Weather https://pekskumar.github.io/Hasmukh_Weather/ Linkdin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hasmukh-shah-4999ba1b3/?originalSubdomain=in

PROJECTS

SOCIAL

ACCOUNT

EDUCATION	Gujarat University	2021
	Gujarat University	2020
	GHSEB HSC	2017
	GHSCE ssc	2015
CERTIFICATES	TOPS Technologies Web Developer & Graphic Designer	(09/2019 - 02/2021)
LANGUAGES	English Gujarati Hindi	
HOBBIES & INTERESTS	Programming Travelling Designing Internet surfing Cricket Painting Reading books	
DECLARATION	I hereby certify that all the information provided here is correct to the best of my knowledge.	